

## Bùi Minh Hoàng



Email recruiter.testloop@gmail.com

Maay sinh 1996-07-19

Ø Giới tính Nam

Số điện thoại 0376435774

Thành phố Hà Nội

🍠 Địa chỉ 90/40 Âu Dương Lân, Phường 3, Quân 8

**CAREER OBJECTIVE** 

Short -Term Target: Have a stable job then become an excellent employee. Along with that will cultivate more experience, life capital. Take advantage of skills, working experience with electrical-electronic expertise and knowledge of electrical and automation systems to become a dedicated, professional person, thereby bringing many sources of value to the company and customers.

Thereby I will contribute to the development of the company.

Always listen and learn every ass

## **EDUCATION**

09/2014 - 07/2017

HOA LU A HIGH SCHOOL |

10/2017 - 01/2022

THUY LOI UNIVERSITY | Faculty of Electrical and Electronics Engineering

Specialization : Electric power system

04/2020 - 06/2020

INDUSTRIAL AUTOMATION CENTER PLCTECH | Mitsubishi PLC

**Programming** 

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

10/2017 - 01/2022

THUY LOI UNIVERSITY | Student

- Design of power supply and lighting.
- Using computers in electrical system analysis.
- Siemens PLC Programming.
- Using Siemens Inverter in three phase motor control.

04/2020 - 06/2020

INDUSTRIAL AUTOMATION CENTER PLCTECH | Student

- Programming real problems re